<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dollarman</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dollarman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/_footer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/_footer/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/posts/nano-consensus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nano-consensus/</guid>
      <description>Nano&amp;rsquo;s innovative transaction and voting process Nano has 3 special protocols that make it different from other cryptocurrencies: 1. Proof of Work is done by each account user to create send and receive blocks and confirm transactions, not by miners or nodes. The PoW difficulty is low enough for personal computers and smartphone to complete in seconds. But it can also be done by a server hosting your wallet without compromising security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/wiki/eos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/wiki/eos/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin - BTC</title>
      <link>/wiki/bitcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/wiki/bitcoin/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crypto without mining</title>
      <link>/posts/nomining/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nomining/</guid>
      <description>Crypto projects without mining There are recent projects in crypto that seek instant transactions with no fees using a technology called DAG.
Notable projects include IOTA, currently ranked #9 in marketcap across all projects and NANO ranked #30.
These projects do not &amp;ldquo;unlock&amp;rdquo; blocks using mining like most other projects, instead IOTA&amp;rsquo;s transactions require every new transaction to confirm 2 of the most recent transactions in a giant registry called the &amp;ldquo;Tangle&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum - ETH</title>
      <link>/wiki/ethereum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/wiki/ethereum/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of Known Scams &amp; Malicious Apps</title>
      <link>/posts/knownscams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/knownscams/</guid>
      <description> Bitcoin:  Twitter scams  NANO:  Bitgrail.com  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Litecoin - LTC</title>
      <link>/wiki/litecoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/wiki/litecoin/</guid>
      <description> About:  Official website: Released on: Created by: Main purpose: Managing Organization: Type of Organization: Country of Origin: How much do developers own?: Types of transactions: Initial Distribution Method(s): Type of network: Can it be mined?: Primary mining tool: Mining Algorithm: Transaction Speed (transactions per second): Average time to confirm transactions: Consensus protocol: Proof of Work Developer activity over last month: Whitepaper:  Online Community Ranking:  Github developer activity: Twitter activity: Reddit activity: Discord chat activity: BitcoinTalk forum activity: News mentions: Google Search Trends:  Distribution of coin supply:  ICO sale: Mining: Airdrop: Expected End Date:  Finance Data:  Total supply: 21,000,000 BTC Marketcap: Trade Volume: Trade Volume change over last day/month/year: Current Price ($USD): Price percent change in last 24hrs: Lowest price in past 30 days: Highest price in 30 days: Exchanges (where to buy):  General Questions:  How many addresses can I make with each seed: Are wallets / addresses reusable: How many seeds are possible: Does it have multisig wallets: Can I give the public address to everyone: Where can I just invest in it without worry: Which exchanges have this coin: Where can I use this coin to buy something: Is this coin legal: Known scam websites and malicious apps: Which one is the address I can share:  Official Social Media Links:  Twitter: Facebook: LinkedIN: Reddit: Discord: BitcoinTalk: Project Roadmap &amp;amp; Update History:  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monero - XMR</title>
      <link>/wiki/monero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/wiki/monero/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nano - NANO</title>
      <link>/wiki/nano/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/wiki/nano/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>/posts/myindex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/myindex/</guid>
      <description> Browse our posts to delve deeper on certain topics. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support this site</title>
      <link>/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/donate/</guid>
      <description>You can support development and upkeep of this site with:
NANO: xrb_1d1rnzocwxntfebx4rjpo738ceom95gez5pa3sa3gwwqhafnrmbhryacoman</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unspent Transaction Outputs (UTXO)</title>
      <link>/posts/reusable-wallet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/reusable-wallet/</guid>
      <description>Unspent Transaction Outputs (UTXO) Bitcoin originated a trasaction system called UTXO or Unspent Transaction Outputs, which reroutes unspent funds from a transaction into a new public address for you. This is because each public address has a private key derived from your seed that must be used to create a transaction. However, the way in which this private spend key is used, makes it easy for a computer to figure it out if used in several transactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Mining?</title>
      <link>/posts/whatismining/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/whatismining/</guid>
      <description>What is Mining? Mining is the process of using vast computing power to unlock the next block in a blockchain and use that block to confirm pending transactions.
Mining is used as a way to achieve consensus in Proof of Work blockchains such as Bitcoin, Ethereum, Monero and most other cryptocurrencies. Consensus means that all the network can agree the mining was done correctly and the trasactions that the minier confirmed are real and stored in the blockchain forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where do you store cryptocurrency?</title>
      <link>/posts/wheretostore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/wheretostore/</guid>
      <description>Where to store cryptocurrency Crypto is not stored anywhere as it is not data. It is simply a really long number that unlocks your money.
You start by generating an extremely long random number called a SEED. usually containing 64 digits mixed with the letters ABCDEF among the digits. This seed alone can unlock all your money no matter what app or website you used to &amp;ldquo;store&amp;rdquo; your cryptocurrency. A wallet is any app or website that takes a seed (or generates one for you) and creates another address known as your wallet address where you can receive funds for a particular currency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where to buy cryptocurrency?</title>
      <link>/posts/wheretobuy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/wheretobuy/</guid>
      <description>Where can I get coins? The easiest way to receive any kind of crypto is simply to ask someone you know to send you some.
Cryptocurrency is &amp;ldquo;bought&amp;rdquo; in websites called exchanges where you exchange it for some of your regular bank currency such as USD. There are exchanges all over the world to cover each country and currency available.
Other Places: Many crypto projects have websites called faucets that give away very small amounts of crypto for newcomers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>